<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title>deibit (pod2g)</title><link>http://deibit.com/</link><description></description><atom:link type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" href="http://deibit.com/categories/pod2g.xml"></atom:link><language>es</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 09:42:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>https://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jailbreaking Apple TV 2 with Seas0nPass (...and overcoming 1600 error)</title><link>http://deibit.com/posts/2012/05/25/jailbreaking-apple-tv-2-with-seas0npass-and-overcoming-1600-error/</link><dc:creator>David García</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://firecore.com/"&gt;Firecore&lt;/a&gt; just released an untethered version of &lt;a href="http://support.firecore.com/entries/387605"&gt;Seas0nPass&lt;/a&gt; (it’s free) for Apple TV 2d Generation. Previously only tethered version worked which might be a bother if the device reboots. Thanks of course to the long awaited &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/pod2g"&gt;pod2g&lt;/a&gt; exploit release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I downloaded the last version and stuck with some issues during the jailbreaking process. This is the infamous 160x iTunes family errors (specifically 1600 and 1601). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, after some tryings and restoring processes I managed to jailbreak my device. Here is the process I did:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- First: If you got any iDevices (iPhones, iPads…) plugged or with Wireless synchronization on, unplug them or put them on flight mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Get your AppleTV 2 and remote control with you, unplug power and HDMI cables and connect your micro-usb to your Mac/Windows. DON’T PLUG USB ON APPLE TV YET!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- After download and execute Seas0nPass, click on “Create IPSW”:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://daganu.files.wordpress.com/2012/05/sp-main2.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="size-full wp-image" src="http://daganu.files.wordpress.com/2012/05/sp-main2.jpg?w=608" alt="Image"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- This will take a while as it is downloading a big .ipsw image. After downloading Seas0nPass will cook the image and when it get ready it will show you this message:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://daganu.files.wordpress.com/2012/05/sp-restore1.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="size-full wp-image" src="http://daganu.files.wordpress.com/2012/05/sp-restore1.jpg?w=608" alt="Image"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Now PLUG THE USB TO YOUR APPLE TV. You will see the little white led blinking SLOWLY so don’t press the buttons yet. When it gets blinking FASTER press the buttons!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- After a few seconds (7 aprox.) you will see the light blinking SLOWLY again. Time to release the buttons and DON’T TOUCH ANYTHING. Just cross your fingers and let iTunes end the process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, the jailbreak should work seamless now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to admit that this is some cargo cult as the real reason why it doesn’t work remains unknown for me. The key happens when entering DFU mode. If the synchronization is not exactly as above…iTunes shows a 1600 error and stop the process. 1600 errors are concerned to the device communication between iTunes, so I think when DFU mode is not running fine it gets out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope your jailbreaking works!   &lt;/p&gt;
</description><category>1600</category><category>1600 error</category><category>apple tv2</category><category>atv2</category><category>firecore</category><category>jailbreak</category><category>jailbreaking</category><category>pod2g</category><category>seas0npass</category><guid>http://deibit.com/posts/2012/05/25/jailbreaking-apple-tv-2-with-seas0npass-and-overcoming-1600-error/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 16:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>